by RentAnAdviser.com
Imagine there′s no heaven
It is easy if you try
No hell below us
Above us only sky
Imagine all the people
living for today
Imagine there′s no countries
It isn′t hard to do
Nothing to kill or die for
And no religion too
Imagine all the people living
life in peace‚ you
You may say I am a dreamer
But I am not the only one
I hope some day you′ll join us
And the world will be as one
Imagine no possessions
I wonder if you can
No need for greed or hunger
A brotherhood of man
Imagine all the people sharing
all the world‚ you
You may say I am a dreamer
But I am not the only one
I hope some day you′ll join us
And the world will be as one
www.RentAnAdviser.com